<!--
<i2p.news date="$Date: 2011-05-16 00:00:00 $">
<i2p.release version="0.8.7" date="2011/06/27" minVersion="0.6" />
-->
<div lang="en">
<h3>2011-06-27: <b>0.8.7 <a href="http://www.i2p2.i2p/release-0.8.7.html">Released</a></b></h3>

<p>I2P release 0.8.7 contains several upgrades to long-neglected components,
 including the Naming Services, graphing, the native CPU ID and BigInteger
 libraries, crypto implementations, and the wrapper.</p>

<p>Thanks to new contributor KillYourTV who was instrumental in implementing
 and testing these upgrades, with additional support from sponge and hottuna.</p>

<p>CPU ID enhancements are by hottuna, generously funded by
 <a href="http://relakks.com/">http://relakks.com/</a> and <a href="http://ipredator.se/">http://ipredator.se/</a> -
 thanks to Peter Sunde and Jan-Erik Fiske for their support.</p>

<p>Also, for the first time, we now have an official
<a href="https://launchpad.net/~i2p-maintainers/+archive/i2p">I2P Personal Package Archive (PPA) on launchpad.net</a>.
For those of you using Ubuntu, this offers an easy way to install I2P and keep the
 various components up-to-date. The I2P package offers the option of installing as
 a service, or it may be started on-demand as usual. This PPA is currently maintained
 by KillYourTV with support by other members of the development team.
The <a href="http://www.i2p2.i2p/debian">Ubuntu/Debian installation instructions</a> are on our website.
</p>

<p>For those updating over the network, this update is about 4 times the usual size,
 due to the inclusion of the jbigi updates. Please be patient while downloading the update over the network.


</p><p>
Please help grow the network.
Say hello to the volunteers on the <a href="irc://127.0.0.1:6668/i2p-help">#i2p-help IRC channel</a>.
<a href="http://www.i2p2.i2p/getinvolved.html">Get involved</a>,
spread the word,
and <a href="http://www.i2p2.i2p/donate.html">donate</a>!
If you find a bug, please enter a report on <a href="http://trac.i2p2.i2p/report/1">trac</a>.
We are still looking for volunteers to work on new and existing translations.
Please volunteer on <a href="irc://127.0.0.1:6668/i2p">IRC #i2p-dev</a>.
</p>
</div>
