<!--
<i2p.news date="$Date: 2012-01-06 00:00:00 $">
<i2p.release version="0.9" date="2012/05/02" minVersion="0.6" />
-->
<div lang="en">
<h3>2012-05-02: <b>0.9 <a href="http://www.i2p2.i2p/release-0.9.html">Released</a></b></h3>

<p>
In the 0.9 release we migrate to Jetty 6 for the console and eepsite web server,
and introduce a simplified router console home page.
This release is network-compatible with prior releases, however see below for important
information on compatibility with existing eepsites, plugins, and webapps.
Upgrading is recommended.
</p>

<p><strong>Update info</strong></p>

<p>  In-network updates and new installs will include Jetty 6, Tomcat, and JSTL.
 PPA (Ubuntu/Debian) updates will have new dependencies for these packages.</p>

<p> If you have not enabled or modified your eepsite settings, the update should automatically migrate you to Jetty 6.
If you do not use Jetty for your eepsite, the update will not affect it.
</p>

<p> If you have more than one Jetty eepsite or you have changed the local port (7658 by default) or otherwise edited jetty.xml,
 you must manually edit the new jetty configuration files after updating, and then restart. </p>

<p>For those with Jetty-based eepsites, we recommend that you verify that the upgrade
was successful and the eepsites are operational after the router restarts.

<p>   Plugin information:
<br />     Plugins not listed below should continue to work under Jetty 6.
<br />     The following plugins require updates for Jetty 6. The router will download and install them a few minutes
      after upgrading: i2pbote, pebble, zzzot
<br />     The following plugins have been renamed and for Jetty 6. Users must manually remove them and download the new versions
      after upgrading: neodatis, seedless
</p>

<p>   Other non-standard console and eepsite webapps not packaged by the I2P development team may or may not
      require modifications.
</p><p>
Say hello to the volunteers on the <a href="irc://127.0.0.1:6668/i2p-help">#i2p-help IRC channel</a>.
<a href="http://www.i2p2.i2p/getinvolved.html">Get involved</a>,
spread the word,
and <a href="http://www.i2p2.i2p/donate.html">donate</a>!
If you find a bug, please enter a report on <a href="http://trac.i2p2.i2p/report/1">trac</a>.
To help on translations,
volunteer on <a href="irc://127.0.0.1:6668/i2p">IRC #i2p-dev</a>
or sign up on <a href="https://www.transifex.net/projects/p/I2P/">Transifex</a>.
</p>
</div>
