<!--
<i2p.news date="$Date: 2012-01-06 00:00:00 $">
<i2p.release version="0.8.13" date="2012/02/27" minVersion="0.6" />
-->
<div lang="en">
<h3>2012-02-27: <b>0.8.13 <a href="http://www.i2p2.i2p/release-0.8.13.html">Released</a></b></h3>

<p>
The 0.8.13 release contains several bug fixes and a couple of new features.
We are pleased that the last release significantly improved performance,
and the network is running well despite continued rapid growth.
Upgrading is recommended.
</p><p>
This is likely to be the last release before 0.9, in which we will migrate to Jetty 6,
and introduce a simplified router console home page. Monitor the news section of
your the router console in the coming weeks for more information on the next release.
</p><p>
Starting with this release, the router will
check for and install plugin updates shortly upon restarting after a router update.
To prevent this, add the <a href="/configadvanced">advanced configuration</a>
<tt>plugins.autoUpdate=false</tt> before restarting.
There is also a new update-all button on <a href="/configclients#plugin">the client configuration page</a>.
</p><p>
Routers in certain countries will now automatically enable hidden mode for increased protection.
However, hidden mode may have lower performance or reliability, and is still a work in progress.
To disable hidden mode before restarting, add the <a href="/configadvanced">advanced configuration</a>
<tt>router.isHidden=false</tt>.
To disable hidden mode later, select <i>use all auto-detect methods</i> under <i>IP Configuration</i> on the
<a href="/confignet">network configuration page</a>.
For the list of countries see <a href="http://zzz.i2p/topics/969">this thread on zzz.i2p</a>.
The only country on the list that has more than one or two I2P users is China.
</p><p>
After you have upgraded, check out the <a href="/i2ptunnel/wizard">new tunnel creation wizard</a>.
</p><p>
Say hello to the volunteers on the <a href="irc://127.0.0.1:6668/i2p-help">#i2p-help IRC channel</a>.
<a href="http://www.i2p2.i2p/getinvolved.html">Get involved</a>,
spread the word,
and <a href="http://www.i2p2.i2p/donate.html">donate</a>!
If you find a bug, please enter a report on <a href="http://trac.i2p2.i2p/report/1">trac</a>.
To help on translations,
volunteer on <a href="irc://127.0.0.1:6668/i2p">IRC #i2p-dev</a>
or sign up on <a href="https://www.transifex.net/projects/p/I2P/">Transifex</a>.
</p>
</div>
